

CONTACT ME AT

- Hai Ba Trung, Ha Noi
- ttdung997@gmail.com
- 093-616-7485
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/d ung-truong-tien-767619136/

SKILLS SUMMARY

- Data analytic coding languages (python, R, SQL, ...)
- Machine learning architecture design
- Background in mathematics
- Building system on Cloud Computing
- Proficiency in multi-tasked, pressured environment.
- Having experience with business intelligence systems

REFERENCE

Tran Quang Duc, Associate Professor, PhD

Head of Cyber Security centre Hanoi University of Science and Technology Email:ductq@soict.hust.edu.vn

Mac Dinh Hieu

AI Team Leader Dasvision Cell: 098-905-7216

DUNG TRUONG

DATA ANALYST

PERSONAL PROFILE

With a background in mathematics, I specialize in analytics and forecasts mostly related to financial analysis. My strongest point is the combination of math and critical thinking and the ability to keep calm under hard pressure to solve problems. With financial problems, I have experience in many separate projects which has achieved domestic and international awards for research. I am confident that I can bring certain values to your company.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Machine Learning Researcher

Dasvision | Jan 2020 - present

- Research in Computer Vision, deploy object detection and object tracking in real-time with high performance
- Working with clients to optimize smart camera on specific requirements

Freelance Data Analysis

Jan 2019 - present

- Perform data clean-up procedure
- Using regression, classification and clustering to solve problem

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

Engineer in Mathematics and Informatics

Hanoi University of Science and Technology | 2015 - 2020

- GPA: 2.89/4.00
- GPA of the latest semester: 3.8/4.00
- Best graduation thesis 2019

HONORS & AWARDS

Amazon Web Services's prize in Angelhack Hackathon Angelhack, Amazon | Jul-2019

Introduce server-less design of business intelligence system on AWS cloud computing

Third Award of Manager Information System Project

ANational Economics University | Jul-2019

Introduce manager information system analyzing and recommend stock speculative, using machine learning method



CONTACT ME AT

- Hai Ba Trung, Ha Noi
- ttdung997@gmail.com
- 093-616-7485
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/d ung-truong-tien-767619136/

DUNG TRUONG

COVER LETTER

Dear TPBank's Chief of HR Department,

I graduated from Hanoi University of Science and Technology with a major in mathematics and information. As a data professional, I am excited and privileged to have found this opportunity of being a data analyst / data scientist at TPBank. As a continuous follower of the finance & analytics field, focus on business intelligence, my qualifications align with the practical and technical skills that you seek. I am certain that I have what you need and would become a beneficial extension to the company.

My best point is the combination of math and critical thinking. I stay calm even when facing the most difficult problems and I never stop thinking until I've found a solution. In addition, I always try to look for a smarter solution to a problem. With my visualization abilities, I would love to automate internal and external reports, creating executive-level dashboards, and presenting information to help executives and others understand the operational impact of the data. I used to win domestic and international awards for research with one of my financial projects. My project, the server-less design system of stock speculative, have won Amazon Web Services's prize in Angelhack Hackathon 2019.

I would be thrilled to work at a fast-pace, proactive working environment like TPBank where my work would be highly beneficial to the organization. Please refer to my attached resume for additional information regarding my proficiencies and achievements. I am positive that I am the best fit for this job and would like to request an interview to follow up on my background and expertise. Given an opportunity, I can assure you that I would be a loyal and valuable employee over the years to come.

Yours sincerely, Dung Truong Tien